<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Image on TooGz&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://toogz.github.io/tags/image/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Image on TooGz&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fr-FR</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 12:29:41 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://toogz.github.io/tags/image/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The &#34;figure&#34; Shortcode</title>
      <link>https://toogz.github.io/posts/the-figure-shortcode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 12:29:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toogz.github.io/posts/the-figure-shortcode/</guid>
      <description>Hugo has figure shortcode built in, so you can easily add figcaptions or hyperlink rel attributes to images. Documentations can be found here:
https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#figure
This theme has 3 CSS classes made for figure elements:
 big: images will break the width limit of main content area. left: images will float to the left. right: images will float to the right.  If a figure has no class set, the image will behave just like a normal markdown image: !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post With Featured Image</title>
      <link>https://toogz.github.io/posts/post-with-featured-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 16:15:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toogz.github.io/posts/post-with-featured-image/</guid>
      <description>Just define the image URL in the content’s front matter, the featured image will be displayed as the background.
For example:
---images:-https://picsum.photos/1024/768/?random--- This is an array, you can set multiple urls, only the first url will be used. These images is also used in Twitter Cards and the Open Graph metadata.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comprendre les 6 licences Creative Commons pour mieux protéger vos photos</title>
      <link>https://toogz.github.io/posts/comprendre-les-6-licences-creative-commons-pour-mieux-proteger-vos-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toogz.github.io/posts/comprendre-les-6-licences-creative-commons-pour-mieux-proteger-vos-photos/</guid>
      <description>Depuis peu, le site de partage de photo 500px est passé à la Creative Commons, ce qui offre une plus grande souplesse dans la gestion des droits de nos images. C&amp;rsquo;est pourquoi je me suis penché sur cette licence dans cet article.
Quatres options de base pour protéger vos oeuvres  Attribution Toutes les licences Creative Commons obligent ceux qui utilisent vos oeuvres à vous créditer de la manière dont vous le demandez, sans pour autant suggérer que vous approuvez leur utilisation ou leur donner votre aval ou votre soutien.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>